Got it, Perospero?
Entering an alliance with
Kaido was my decision.
Be that as it may,
your family has long dreamed of the day
that you become the Pirate King, Mama!
Lick!
I know that, of course.
Can't you all just trust me on this?
Okay...
Well, that's a relief.
I see.
I suppose this means our ogre-hunting party
has officially disbanded, Perospero?
Even though I accepted your offer.
Marco!
I can't believe you're helping those punks.
I thought better of you.
The remnants of Whitebeard's crew
must truly be lost without their captain.
I don't think you know what
"remnant" truly means, Big Mom!
Do you really think...
we're still bound to Pops' will?
Those of us left behind...
are free!
True... dead men give no orders.
You're free to act out.
That's not quite it...
I'm free to do whatever I want!
I knew it was him!
Carrot! Where are you going?!
He was there! Pedro's killer!
Now's your chance, Straw Hat! Go!
Thanks!
The whole island is in chaos.
Are they gonna come all the way up here?
I can't believe no one's
here in the tatami room!
Would you sing us a song, Big Sis Maria?
All right.
How about this?
♪ On a snowy night... ♪
Wait!
♪ ...two yearning lovers... ♪
♪ kept apart by fate... ♪
♪ kept apart by circumstance... ♪
♪ will finally meet again! ♪
♪ Under the moonlight... ♪
So romantic!
♪ ...their passion... ♪
♪ burning! ♪
Master Kin!
Kin!
I will avenge Lord Oden!
Take this!
You really wanna die that badly?
Kin!
What?!
You guys are not Oden after all.
Pretending to be great samurai
from the safety of Oden's shadow,
and even now, after his death,
you still play at being samurai.
What can you do?
If you think we're just playing at being
samurai, why not fight us and find out?!
All right... Bring it on!
Attack!
Crimson Cat Dance!
Kappa Style...
Celestial Torrent!
What?!
Canine Scourge!
Lingering Snow Scythes!
Slicing Rounds!
What's this?!
Their attacks aren't even close
to the level of Oden's swordplay.
How can they cut me?!
Kaido!
Do it!
I said, do it!
Ninpo: Scroll-Scroll Technique!
My scroll will roll up anything!
And now, I return it to you...
Blast Breath...
Restoration!
So you want to kill me?
You're just a bunch of cowardly retainers...
chasing your Lord Oden's phantom!
He is right.
We have always been cowards.
I shall teach you how to use
the Oden two-sword style!
No thank you.
We possess our own style...
But why?! This is the Oden two-sword style!
Do you not want to inherit it?!
Of course we wanted to inherit it.
Everyone insisted they were his first disciple.
There was a serious fight to determine
who was his first student.
We all loved Oden so much,
it looked like a fight to the death.
– Oden...
– Two-Sword Style!
Is this your idea of a joke?
Such pathetic imitations!
Listen, guys!
Ryuo is...
Listen to me!
We have honed our skills with the blade,
all for this day when we save Wano!
Flame-Rend!
Do not underestimate... my samurai!
People will remember your
heroic death for generations.
They can forget me for all I care!
My spirit will live on!
– Oden Two-Sword Style:
– Halcyon Totsuka!
Sing! Dance!
Be merry! For today is the Fire Festival!
The Flower Capital is the lone place
that flourishes in Wano.
However, like the rest of the country,
its population hides terror and tension
behind a thin veneer of frivolity.
"Someday, the Kozuki samurai
will save this country."
They could carry on...
because they all believed
in such a seemingly true legend.
Delicious!
That really hits the spot!
The Fire Festival sure is fun...
Yes...
It takes me back to the good old days.
I wish today would go on just like this...
forever and ever...
So tasty!
We get to drink such clean water.
What a luxury!
The air is so fresh...
Let's really take it in.
Once the festival ends, it's back to sobriety...
for a whole 'nother year!
Dammit!
If only Orochi wasn't backed by Kaido!
No one's gonna get killed today.
What a wonderful day!
Orochi will be back tomorrow, though!
I bet the Kozuki Clan
is fighting them right now!
Oh, that's interesting,
even if it's complete horseshit!
Tell me more!
Alright then! They've brought back
warriors from all over the world,
and they're at Onigashima right now,
slicing up Orochi and Kaido and creating chaos!
Keep going! Keep going!
Today's the day to share wild fantasies!
S-So cold...!
Help me!
This is bad...
Stay away from them!
Fall back!
Get away from them!
The samurai are splitting up... Why?
This must be that plague of his...
You'll turn into an ogre just by touching them.
It's highly contagious...
How could he spread such a virus?
He's the real ogre here!
Seal off the exits to the other floors!
This floor is done for!
This is my masterpiece!
Plague rounds:
Ice Ogre!
Outta my way!
You damn cockroach!
I said "Outta my way"!
Wait, Luffy!
What are you doing?!
You're gonna fight Kaido, right?
Save your energy for now!
Off with Straw Hat's head!
Outta the way, swirly brows!
Let's do it!
I can handle all of you brutes by myself!
Party Table Kick Course!
Damn you!
How dare you do that to my men?!
You're not getting past me!
Prepare yourself!
Why's the gorilla growing
from there?! It's weird!
Is that so?!
Then how exactly should a gorilla...
grow out of someone?!
How would I know?!
Gorilla Punch Punch!
Wow!
He's tougher than he looks!
That Gorilla Punch is so cool!
Water Shot!
Oh! Jinbe!
I thought I would find you around here.
Looks like I was right...
Briscola!
Are you all right?
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey! Are you okay?!
Stay with me!
Hey, you!
How dare you attack us!
Alright! It's my turn now!
Come on! How many times do I have
to tell you to save your energy?!
You'll take too long beating up this many guys!
Shut up!
I'll polish them off in ten seconds!
Any complaints?
Yeah! It'd only take three
seconds if I was there!
Hey, stop ignoring me!
Prepare yourselves!
Gorilla Punch Punch!
Fishman Karate: Shark Tile Fist!
Briscola!
Oh, nice one!
You're awesome, Jinbe!
Luffy!
I'll escort you to the rooftop!
You need to save your energy for now!
Why are you taking control?!
I've already taken Luffy this far!
I see. My apologies!
Luffy! Our samurai allies
should be up there already!
Let's meet up with them!
Alright! Got it!
How the hell are you so on top of everything?
How dare you take down Briscola?!
Get them!
Look... Luffy will jump at
any opportunity to fight.
Let's keep on our toes then!
Wait!
What's the situation, Bao Huang?
Right, so, Yamato and Momonosuke
are headed outside through the Right-Brain Tower!
That's good enough.
This is King.
We've ascertained the identities of
the idiots who crashed the banquet.
The enemy's army numbers around 5,400.
The majority are samurai,
led by Oden's retainers.
It would seem...
the Kozuki Clan has staked its prestige...
in an attempt to restore their name.
They want to make Oden's son,
Kozuki Momonosuke, the shogun of Wano.
To all available Gifters
and Soaring Six members...
my orders are as follows:
Kill Kozuki Momonosuke, who is currently
escaping through the Right-Brain Tower,
and bring me his head!
This will destroy the samurai's morale.
Of course, I know the pirates
are another matter altogether.
Our orders are to kill him,
not to bring him in...
That makes things easier.
Shoot.
Fetch me his corpse!
– Yes, sir!
Here it is.
Huh? What's this?
A barrel?
The Armored Division's defenses
cannot be broken by such a weapon!
Shinobu!
You mustn't!
Please stay hidden!
Nice try!
Every member of our squad
has an armored body.
There's no way out!
Aim for the kid!
Lord Momonosuke!
Please... run...
Shinobu...
I'll kill you...
along with the brat!
You can't even shield him!
Shinobu!
Ru...
Run, Lord Momonosuke!
Run?
Is that what a shogun is supposed to do?
Shinobu! Shinobu!
You're mine!
I beg you...!
I beg you!
Well, well...
Are you sure you want to interfere,
Young Master Yamato?
I'm not interfering.
I'm here to fight for the Kozuki.
For I... am Oden!
Cut his throat!
We haven't won until we've removed
his head from his neck!
You are right!
Sever Kaido's windpipe!
Within your spirit, I saw
the shadow of Kozuki Oden...
It wouldn't have been a bad death...
Every time this scar aches,
I remember that fateful day...
Help!
Father!
Father, save me!
Guess who!
If only no one had interfered
at that exact moment...
But you guys are not Oden after all...
There will never be another
monstrous samurai like him!
It's too shallow!
You aren't even strong enough
to reopen the old scar!
None of you are!
Invisible slashes?!
– Kiku!